

LORENZO RIGATO

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

A dedicated 26 years old full-stack developer with 5+ years of experience in web and mobile apps development.

Strong knowledge on Ruby on Rails and Android technologies.

Passionate on data engineering.

Able to complete projects efficiently and satisfying customer's requirements.

Clean code lover and beautiful UI fascinated.

CONTACT



llollox.github.com



lore91tanz@gmail.com



+39 333 8600532



Viale Brigata Marche, 33 Treviso, 31100

PERSONAL SKILLS

MOTIVATION

QUICK LEARNER

TEAMWORK

PROBLEM SOLVING



WORK EXPERIENCE

REACT JS DEVELOPER

Foodracers srl - Treviso, Italy

Ago 2017 to Current

Development of a responsive application to buy food from restaurants in React JS

ANDROID & IOS DEVELOPER

Previnet SPA - Treviso, Italy

Nov 2016 to Current

Development of an application for a bank on both Android & iOS platforms about managing health services.

WEB DEVELOPER

REPLY SPA - Milan, Italy

Apr 2016 to Oct 2016

Development of DirectLine's web application in Liferay.

ANDROID DEVELOPER

BELKA SRL - Trento, Italy

Jan 2016 to Mar 2016

Development of two Android applications. First about sharing events between friends. Second on chips configuration via NFC.

RUBY ON RAILS AND ANDROID DEVELOPER

FONDAZIONE BRUNO KESSLER - Trento, Italy

Dec 2011 to Dec 2015

- Design and development of Ruby on Rails and Android applications against food waste.
- Worked closely with senior developers. Learned advanced programming and project management skills.



EDUCATION

COMPUTER SCIENCE MASTER DEGREE

UNIVERSITY OF TRENTO 110 CUM LAUDE / 110

December 2015

COMPUTER SCIENCE BACHELOR DEGREE

UNIVERSITY OF TRENTO 103 / 110 September 2013



iOS

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

ANDROID		

RUBY ON RAILS

USER INTERACTION & UX

ANGULAR JS

ADOBE CS6